<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="34">
    <author>Decker_MMIV (DCK)</author>
    <author_contact>fs-uk.com, modcentral.co.uk, forum.farming-simulator.com</author_contact>

<!--
    NOTE: For contributing translations, DO NOT edit this ModDesc.XML.
          Only modify the corresponding ModDesc_l10n_*.XML file.
-->
    <contributors>
        SchorschiBW, ja_pizgam, Gonimy_Vetrom, JakobT, pokers, gighen, SicFR57, Alfredo Prieto,
        Vanquish081, Dzi4d3k, shermy, mngrazy
    </contributors>

    <version>1.0.0.28</version>

    <title>
        <en>Glance</en>
        <de>Glance</de>
        <pl>Glance</pl>
        <ru>Glance</ru>
        <hu>Glance</hu>
        <it>Glance</it>
        <fr>Glance</fr>
        <es>Glance</es>
        <nl>Glance</nl>
    </title>

    <description>
        <en>
<![CDATA[A notification-and-status utility that can be configured to show only what you need to see.

Note: Visible when the F1-helpbox is off!
]]>
        </en>
        <de>
<![CDATA[Ein Mitteilungs- und Status-Tool das so konfiguriert werden kann dass man  nur das sieht was man braucht.

Hinweis: Sichtbar, wenn die F1-Hilfebox deaktiviert ist!
]]>
        </de>
        <pl>
<![CDATA[Użyteczne narzędzie powiadamiania i statusu, które może być skonfigurowane tak, aby pokazywać to, co chcesz zobaczyć.

Uwaga: Widoczne kiedy F1-helpbox jest wyłączony!
]]>
        </pl>
        <ru>
<![CDATA[Утилита для отображения уведомлений/статуса техники и животных. Может работать в соответствии с настройками, чтобы показывать только то, что Вы хотите видеть.

Примечание: Видимая, когда F1-HelpBox выключен!
]]>
        </ru>
        <hu>
<![CDATA[Egy állapot- és tevékenység kijelző mód, amiben te magad választhatod meg mit szeretnél látni.

Megjegyzés: Látható, ha az F1-helpbox ki van kapcsolva!
]]>
        </hu>
        <it>
<![CDATA[Un servizio di notifica e stato che può essere configurato per mostrare solo quello che hai bisogno di vedere

Nota: visibile quando la F1-HelpBox è spento!]]>
        </it>
        <fr>
<![CDATA[Un utilitaire de notification et statut qui peut être configuré pour afficher ce que vous voulez.

Remarque: visible lorsque la F1-helpbox est désactivée!
]]>
        </fr>
        <es>
<![CDATA[Muestra notificaciones sobre el estado de las tareas y puede configurarse para mostrar solo aquello que se necesite

Nota: ¡Visible cuando la F1-ayuda está apagada!
]]>
        </es>
        <nl>
<![CDATA[Een notificatie en status tool welke geconfigureerd kan worden zodat je alleen ziet wat je nodig bent.

Let op: Zichtbaar wanneer de F1-HelpBox is uitgeschakeld!
]]>
        </nl>
    </description>

    <iconFilename>store_Glance.dds</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>

    <l10n filenamePrefix="modDesc_l10n" /> <!-- Load the corresponding modDesc_l10n_<language>.XML file, or revert to 'en'/'de'. -->

    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="Glance.lua" />
    </extraSourceFiles>

    <inputBindings>
        <input visible="true" name="GLANCE_MORE" category="ONFOOT VEHICLE" key1="KEY_lalt KEY_m" />
        <input visible="true" name="GLANCE_LESS" category="ONFOOT VEHICLE" key1="KEY_lalt KEY_l" />
    </inputBindings>
</modDesc>
